<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Operate on English</title>
    <link>/70_operate.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Operate on English</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/70_operate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deployment</title>
      <link>/70_operate/1_deployment.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/70_operate/1_deployment.html</guid>
      <description>Deploy the Cluster Agent to EKS It&amp;rsquo;s time to deploy the Cluster Agent to the EKS cluster. Let&amp;rsquo;s start by looking at the script that deploys the Cluster Agent to the cluster using the commands below in your Cloud9 terminal:
cd /opt/appdynamics/workshopuser cat -n deployClusterAgent.sh The script is performing the following actions: - Changing to the directory where the agent YAML files reside - Creates a namespace for the agent - Deploys the Cluster Agent Operator - Creates the Access Key for the agent - Deploys the Cluster Agent - Deploys the Kubernetes Metric Server</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cognition Engine</title>
      <link>/70_operate/2_cognition_engine.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/70_operate/2_cognition_engine.html</guid>
      <description>What is Cognition Engine? Cognition Engine is a collection of machine learning algorithms that give you the power to automate anomaly detection and root cause analysis, drive intelligent alerting and dramatically reduce mean time to resolution (MTTR) through insights and automated actions.
With AppDynamics you can unlock the power of machine learning and AI to navigate the complexity of the digital first world and deliver a world-class user experience with our patented Cognition Engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cluster Agent</title>
      <link>/70_operate/3_cluster_agent.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/70_operate/3_cluster_agent.html</guid>
      <description>The AppDynamics Cluster Agent enables Ginas&amp;rsquo; CloudOps team to get deep level visibility into EKS clusters, including every node, pod, and namespace down to the container level. The Cluster Agent utilizes the existing Kubernetes Metrics Server API to bring back key performance data at the cluster, namespace, and node level. The agent displays metrics on Events, Pods, Deployments, Daemon-sets, Jobs, Services, Service Endpoints, Quotas, Configs, Containers, and Resource Limits.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
