<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wrapup on English</title>
    <link>/80_wrapup.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wrapup on English</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/80_wrapup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Workshop Cleanup</title>
      <link>/80_wrapup/1_workshop_teardown.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/80_wrapup/1_workshop_teardown.html</guid>
      <description>Congratulations! &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; You have successfully completed the Advanced Observability with AppDynamics workshop! &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Before we start the teardown process, please complete this survey and let us know how you liked the workshop. The feedback you provide will help us with improving this workshop along with future workshops. 
In order to prevent charges to your AWS account, we recommend cleaning up the infrastructure that was created. If you plan to keep things running so you can examine the workshop a bit more, please remember to do the cleanup when you are done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud9 Cleanup</title>
      <link>/80_wrapup/2_cloud9_cleanup.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/80_wrapup/2_cloud9_cleanup.html</guid>
      <description>Make sure you have run the teardown script in the previous section before deleting your Cloud9 instance. If you delete your Cloud9 instance before running the teardown script, the resources created in your AWS account for the workshop must be removed manually with the AWS Console.
 Navigate to the cloud9 console or just search for it under the AWS console services menu.
 Ensure the AppD-Workshop environment is selected, then click the Delete button</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survey</title>
      <link>/80_wrapup/3_survey.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/80_wrapup/3_survey.html</guid>
      <description>To help us improve this product, please take some time to fill out the Survey</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
